show up at the court what you have to
preséntate en el jugado lo que tienes
do
que hacer
Loli let's
Loli a
see there the climb began there the climb
ver ahí empezó la trepa ahí ya la trinc
the climb let's go It's been a while
la trepa vamos Ya llevaba tiempo
eh based on blood and lies bye
eh a base de sangre y de mentiras chao
see you in another
rdes nos vemos en otro
video more more and better better worse you
vídeo más más y mejor mejor peor
want to Browse the
quieres Navegar de forma segura en
internet safely and also access all the
internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix HBO Max or Disney Plus
como nefli hbo Max o Disney Plus
cyberghost VPN And I don't know if you
cyberghost VPN Y es que no sé si lo
know but there is content that is not available in your country
sabes pero hay contenidos que en tu país
and with this little
no están disponibles y con este
trick you can access all the
truquillo puedes acceder a todo el
content wherever you are I don't know if you
contenido estés donde estés no sé si
know what a VPN is but it is an
sabes lo que es una VPN pero es una
extension that you put on your internet with
extensión que le pones a tu internet con
which you mask the IP and apart from
la que en mascaras la IP y aparte de
browsing completely safely and anonymously
Navegar completamente seguro y anónimo
without anyone being able to know who you are and
sin que nadie pueda saber quién eres y
where you are it helps you access
dónde estás Te sirve para acceder a
some content that is blocked
algunos contenidos que están bloqueados
in your country there are movies and series on your
en tu país hay películas y series en tus
favorite platforms that are not
plataformas favoritas que no están
available there are television programs
disponible hay programas de televisión
for example on mediaset content that
por ejemplo en mediaset contenidos que
if you try to watch them outside of Spain
si los intentas ver fuera de España
they have a geoblock that does not
tienen un geobloqueo que no te lo
allow you Well with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that's
permite Pues con Cyber Ghost VPN eso se
over Apart from being  protected
acabó Aparte de estar protegido
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet in addition you will have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data Ultra fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad Ultra rápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live broadcasts without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of an 83%
quieras además aprovecha to un 83 por de
discount using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
watch out because you can try cyberghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar cyberghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced you ask for a refund and they
convence pides el reembolso y te
will return the piece So don't wait any longer
devuelven la pza Así que no esperes más
to protect your connection and improve your
para proteger tu conexión y aumentar tu
internet experience run and click on the
experiencia en internet corre yle click
link in the description and take
al enlace de la descripción y aprovecha
advantage of this super offer cyberghost VPN to browse completely free and secure we continue with the video yes it was very little the day that she donated the most It was on a birthday of hers yes no there were several times that she donated well I remember that there was a live broadcast in which she donated a lot that Marina was
en el que donó mucho que estaba Marina
on the street I don't remember what event
en la calle no me acuerdo en Qué evento
and there was a live broadcast in which she donated
y hubo un directo en el que ella donó A
Maybe she donated 600 in the  live Okay
lo mejor donó 600 en el directo Vale
but no it wasn't
pero no no ha
your idea that there were those two or three
sido de tú que hubiese esos dos o tres
months for maybe she would
meses para lo mejor ella
donate 1 each month between all the
donara 1 cada mes entre todos los
live shows ok of which I got
directos vale de los cuales me llegaba
30% less you understand I mean no it
el 30% menos me entiendes O sea no no
wasn't a significant amount of money we're not
era un dinero significativo a mí no me
going to see my family
vamos a ver familia
to me my salary is not significant that
a mí mi sueldo no es significativo que
a person who has to be
una persona que haya que yo tenga que
like for example we've seen the
estar como por ejemplo hemos visto la
climber not being the one she keeps quiet I
trepa no siendo
don't know what to call it of this
la la calla no sé cómo llamarlo de esta
lady
señora
putting up with the whole thing
aguantándolo el rollo en todo
making up the c that she made up I mean I
inventándose el c que se inventado o sea
no I no I I have my community
yo no yo no yo yo tengo mi comunidad
what makes me is not having one
a mí lo que me hace es no tener a una
person who donates a lot but having
persona que done mucho sino tener a
many who donate a
muchos que donen un
little bit not having a person who
poquito no tener a una persona que
seems to be here that is your owner you know no
parezca aquí que sea tu dueño sabes no
no this person owns the channel
no esta persona se adueña del canal se
owns the opinions because they are
adueña de las opiniones porque te está
giving you a salary No man no no I am
dando un suerdo No hombre no no yo
grateful of if they want to donate The
agradecido de de si quiere donar Cuanto
more they donate the better you know but the nice thing is
más done mejor sabes pero lo bonito es
that one one here ro puts a super chat
que uno uno aquí ro ponga un super chat
of
de
2 lizardo puts a super chat of 5
2 lizardo ponga un super chat de 5
E you know another of 1 euro another of  10 another of
E sabes otro de 1 eur otro de 10 otro de
20 but between all So since there are so
20 pero entre todos Entonces como somos
many of us then my
muchos pues entonces mi
salary you know but you can't depend on
sueldo sabes pero no puedes depender de
one but what you have that you have a
uno sino lo que tienes que tenéis una
community that respects you there is no more
comunidad que te
this one we take it away now bye bye
este nos lo quitamos ya chao chao
kisses let's see wait based on it
besitos a ver espérate a base de es que
was on Agatha's Twitter no about we have
estaba en el Twitter de Agatha no lo de
stayed before you were going to look for it
nos hemos quedado antes ibas a buscarlo
and we have stayed before with this that we did
y nos hemos quedado antes con esto que
n't see it this new year for this
no lo vimos este año nuevo para este
2025 Jordi and Victoria I wish you I wish that
2025 Jordi y Victoria os deseo os deseo
calm falls on you and that the
que os caiga el calma y que os
same thing happens to you the same thing that you
pase lo mismo lo mismo que vosotros
are doing with people with me
estáis haciendo con con la gente conmigo
and with more
y con más
people
gente
Eh I hope I hope Jordi and I hope
Eh espero espero Jordi y espero
Victoria that you have everything well
Victoria que lo tengáis todo bien
collected that you have everything with good
recogido que lo tengáis todo con buenas
evidence
pruebas
because exposing people and talking about
porque hacer exponer a gente y hablar de
anonymous people talking about bank accounts
anónima hablar de cuentas corrientes
talking about abuse of the
hablar de un maltrato a personas
elderly Loli that you are not going to report
mayores Loli que no vas a denunciar a
anyone really it is ridiculous to
nadie de verdad es que esta ridículo de
start playing a role of I hope you
ponerte a a hacer un papel de Espero que
can verify everything you have not
lo puedas comprobar todo no has
reported It was to ABC that you have not reported on the
denunciado A la ABC no has denunciado al
fly  8000 times that you were going to
vuelo las 8000 veces que le ibas a
report him you don't show up for the
denunciar no te presentas a las
reports that you have filed you
denuncias que tienes puestas tú
talk
hablar
eh insinuate that you're going to come that You're going to
eh insinuar que vas a venir que Vais a
go to someone's house that you're
ir a la casa de alguien que estáis por
around being who you are and with what
el entorno siendo quién sois y con lo
you already have on top of you Jordi that's what
que tú ya tienes encima Jordi que de eso
really cracks us up that you talk to us you don't
sí que nos parte que nos hables no te
entertain yourself much talking about others
entretienes mucho hablando de los demás
and you don't tell what it is that you have on
y no cuentas Qué es lo que tienes tú
top of you my wishes for this year is that
encima mis deseos para este año es que
you manage to reconcile again in the form
consigas volver a reconciliarte en forma
of being able to see those people again of
de poder volver a ver a esas personas
course then it's that one wants to because of
claro luego está que uno quiera porque
course those of the happy life may be
claro los de la vida alegre igual está
a little more the same no that always eh you have
un poquito más igual no que siempre eh
simply made use of them for
simplemente has hecho uso de ellos para
when it has interested you eh more vium more
cuando te ha interesado eh más vium más
super chat more
super chat más
and more and more
más y más y más
and that you wasted a little more of your what
y que marastes un poco más de tu lo que
you can achieve and of your time to the
puedes conseguir y de tu tiempo a a las
things that really belong to your environment
cosas que de verdad son de tu entorno
than to a person Manik who is not worth
que a un una persona manik que no vale
even to believed an
ni ni para creí un
egg u and you Victoria eh
huevo u y tú Victoria eh
and
y
I wish I wish that you understand that
Deseo deseo que entiendas
women have fought and have
que que las mujeres han peleado y han
struggled
luchado
a lot  Happy New Year Javi Thank you so much
mucho Feliz año Javi Muchísimas gracias
for the company you've kept me in a
por la compañía que me has hecho en una
difficult time of my
época difícil de mi
life Cara blowing a kiss I'm already more
vida Cara lanzando un beso ya vengo más
powerful when we come back from Three Kings Day okay
potente cuando vengamos de Reyes vale
today
hoy
I am and more I'm going to leave in no time I don't know
estoy y más me voy a ir en nada no sé
what else I have left, I have left
qué más me
oh the loser we have to
quedó me queda ay el pringado tenemos
see something of the loser
que ver algo del pringao
Don't look at the the Pilar Vera eh he continues with his thing
No mira la la Pilar Vera eh sigue a lo
his
suyo a su
roll you have announced lawsuits things are getting
rollo has anunciado querellas la cosa Va
serious I mean at what moment how do you have to
seria o sea en qué momento cómo tienes
be how do you have to be What What What
que estar cómo tienes que estar Qué Qué
kind of person do you have to be for you to
Qué tipo de gente tienes que ser para
see this
que veas a esta
woman in these videos and see that this is
mujer en estos vídeos y veas que esto es
an announcement of a serious lawsuit Agatha has
un anuncio de querell serio Agatha ha
announced lawsuits things are getting serious and
anunciado querellas la cosa Va seria y
Pilar Vera were expected Yes yes of course
la Pilar Vera eran esperadas Sí sí claro
well the poor woman It's that we're going we're going
bueno la pobre mujer Es que ya vamos
from drawer to drawer come on I have
vamos de cajón de cajón vamos no me cabe
no doubt that roli has every
la menor duda que que roli tiene todo su
right to use the law
derecho utilizar la ley
come on this is real what a little thing she has a
vamos esto es de verdad qué cosita tiene
battery it's been a while since we
pila hace tiempo que no la
saw her uploaded she doesn't keep uploading doing me
vemos subida no sigue suba haciendo yo
no
no
she goes around all
ella va el
day looking for publications about me look
día buscando publicaciones sobre mí mira
and commenting on it
y comentándolo
look she didn't like the rewind either
mira tampoco le ha gustado el rewind
and they fear Tania's t and they fear him that's why they
y lo temen al t de Tania y lo temen por
walk like that how are you Oh Really what a
eso andan así qué tal Ay De verdad qué
ridiculous thing What a
ridícula Qué cosa más
ridiculous thing with all the
Absurda con todas las cuentas de de los
stalker accounts eh
acosadores eh
Wilson
Wilson
Ah but she puts emojis it's like reviewed
Ah pero pone emojis es como revisado
shared she's putting
compartido va poniendo
emojis I did because I didn't know This
emojis yo hacía ya que no sabía Esta
lady I don't know the days
señora no sé los días
Eh you see
Eh lo ves
they are with The
están con Los
Greats
Grandes
Ah with The Greats in quotes that
Ah con Los Grandes entre comillas que a
Pilar veran thinks that making a video
Pilar veran le parece que hacer un vídeo
with Auron with Dross with Iker Jiménez no they are not
con auron con Dross con Iker Jiménez no
the greats they are
no son los grandes son
great that she has those people in the
grandes que ella tiene esa gente en el
space every
space todos los
day everything everything everything everything
días todo todo todo todo
that she is a lady is that oh she gives me the
que es una señora es que ay me da un
creeps and I don't know what that
repelo y un no sé qué esa
lady I'm going to see the loser's thing and and I'm
señora voy a ver lo del pringao y y me
going to go to the kids eh
voy a ir a la chavalería eh